http://www.saisystems.com/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
x
Protecting your private information is our priority.  This Statement of Privacy applies to www.saisystems.com and Saisystems
International Inc. and governs data collection data collection and usage.  For the purposes of this Privacy Policy,
unless otherwise noted, all references to Saisystems International Inc.
include: Saisystems International Inc., Saisystems Health, Saisystems
Technology, Saisystems Digital www.saisystems.com,  www.saisystemstech.com, www.saisystemshealth.com, www.saisystemsdigital.com.
The Saisystems websites are informational and contain
information regarding the company, its products and service offerings and
related industries.  By using the
Saisystems websites, you consent to the data practices described in this
statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
To better provide you with products and services offered on
our sites, Saisystems may collect personally identifiable information such as
your:
products and services
We do not collect any personal information about you unless you
voluntarily provide it to us.  However,
you may be required to provide certain personal information to us when you
elect to use certain products or services available on the site.  These may include: (a) registering for an
account on our site; (b) entering a sweepstakes or contest sponsored by us or
one of our partners; (c) signing up for special offers from selected third
parties; (d) sending us email messages.
To wit, we will use your information for, but not limited to,
communicating with you in relation to services and/or products you have
requested from us.  We also may gather
additional personal or non-personal information in the future.
Use of your Personal Information
Saisystems collects and uses your personal information to
operate its websites and deliver the services you have requested.
Saisystems may also use your personally identifiable
information to inform you of other products or services available from
Saisystems and its affiliates.
Sharing Information with Third Parties
Saisystems does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists
to third parties.
Saisystems may share data with trusted partners to help perform
statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support,
or arrange for deliveries.  All such
parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide
these services to Saisystems, and they are required to maintain the
confidentiality of your information.
Saisystems may disclose your personal information, without
notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such
action is necessary to: (a) confirm to the edicts of the law or comply with
legal process on Saisystems or the sites; (b) protect and defend the rights or
property of Saisystems; and /or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect
the personal safety of users of Saisystems, or the public.
Tracking User Behavior
Saisystems may keep track of the websites and pages our
users visits with Saisystems, in order to determine what Saisystems services
are the most popular. This data is used to deliver content and advertising
within Saisystems to customers whose behavior indicates that they are
interested in a particular subject area.
Automatically Collected Information
Information about your computer hardware and software may be
automatically collected by Saisystems.
This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain
names, access times and referring website addresses.  This information is used for the operation of
the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general
statistics regarding use of the Saisystems websites.
Use of Cookies
The Saisystems website may use “cookies” to help you
personalize your online experience.  A
cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page
server.  Cookies cannot be used to run
programs or deliver viruses to your computer.
Cookies are uniquely assigned to you and can only be read by a web
server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a
convenience feature to save you time.
The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned
to a specific page.  For example, if you
personalize Saisystems pages, or register with Saisystems site or services a
cookie helps Saisystems to recall your specific information on subsequent
visits.  This simplifies the process of
recording your personal information, such as billing address, shipping
addresses, and so on.  When you return to
the same Saisystems website, the information you previously provided can be
retrieved, so you can easily use Saisystems features that you customized.
Saisystems uses Google Analytics to analyze the use of this
website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about
website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users’ computers. The
information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about
the use of the website. Google will store this information.
Saisystems reserves the right to use Google’s remarketing
tools.  AdWords Remarketing is a
Remarketing and Behavioral Targeting service provided by Google. It connects
the activity of www.Saisystemsroup.com with the Adwords advertising network and
the Doubleclick Cookie.  It enables
Saisystems to advertise products and services you may be interested on
participating sites as you browse the internet.
An appropriate description of how you’re using remarketing or similar
audiences to advertise online. Third-party vendors, including Google, show our
ads on sites across the Internet. These third-party vendors, including Google,
use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits our website. You can
opt out of Google’s use of cookies here:
http://google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout?hl=en
Google’s privacy policy is available at:
http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html.
In addition, as you browse parknewhaven.com, advertising
cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are
interested in.  Our display advertising
partner, AdRoll, then enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on
other sites based on your previous interaction with Saisystemsroup.com. The
techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your
name, email address, postal address or telephone number. You can email info@saisystems.com to opt out of AdRoll
and their partners’ targeted advertising.
Most browsers allow you to reject all cookies, whilst some
browsers allow you to reject just third-party cookies. For example, in Internet
Explorer (version 9) you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet
options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block All Cookies” using the sliding
selector. Blocking all cookies will, however, have a negative impact upon the
usability of many websites, including this one.
Links and Third-Party Applications
Saisystems is not responsible for the contents of any such
linked site. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by Saisystems
of the site. Use of any such linked website is at the user's own risk. For
example, this Website may provide direct links to client websites or social
networking services. You acknowledge that Saisystems has no control over and is
not responsible for the availability of any such third-party applications,
websites, content, or resources, which are made available by companies or
persons other than Saisystems. You further acknowledge that Saisystems is not
liable to you for any loss or damage which may be incurred by you as a result
of these third-party applications, websites, content, or resources.
Children under Thirteen
We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information
from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register for
the Service (as that term is defined in our Terms of Use. If you are under 13,
please do not attempt to register for the Service or send any information about
yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email
address. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to us or on
the Service. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal
information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent,
we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we
might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at info@saisystems.com.
External Data Storage Sites
We may store your data on servers provided by third-party
hosting vendors with whom we have contracted.
Changes to this Privacy Policy.
We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of
information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the
time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we use Personal
Information, we will notify you by posting a notice on the Site, on or through
the Service, or by sending an email to the email address associated with your
account. You are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when you use the service
after such changes have been first posted.
Questions, CONCERNS AND DISPUTE RESOLUTION.
If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy
policies, please send us a detailed message to info@saisystems.com. We will
make every effort to resolve your concerns. Any disputes arising from this
Privacy Policy, or from the use or processing of any Personal Information we
obtain from you in connection with the Service, shall be handled in accordance
with the Dispute Resolution terms set forth in the Company’s Terms of Use,
available at www.saisystems.com/terms-of-use.
Contact Information
Saisystems welcomes your questions or comments regarding
this Statement of Privacy.  If you
believe that Saisystems has not adhered to this statement, please contact
Saisystems at:
Saisystems International Inc.
Font Primary
---'Arial', Helvetica, sans-serif'Arial Black', Gadget, sans-serif'Bookman Old Style', serif'Comic Sans MS', cursive'Courier', monospace'Garamond', serif'Georgia', serif'Impact', Charcoal, sans-serif'Lucida Console', Monaco, monospace'Lucida Sans Unicode', Lucida Grande, sans-serif'MS Sans Serif', Geneva, sans-serif'MS Serif', New York, sans-serif'Palatino Linotype', Book Antiqua, Palatino, serif'Tahoma',Geneva, sans-serif'Times New Roman', Times, serif'Trebuchet MS', Helvetica, sans-serif'Verdana', Geneva, sans-serifABeeZeeAbelAbril FatfaceAclonicaAcmeActorAdaminaAdvent ProAguafina ScriptAkronimAladinAldrichAlefAlegreyaAlegreya SCAlex BrushAlfa Slab OneAliceAlikeAlike AngularAllanAllertaAllerta StencilAlluraAlmendraAlmendra DisplayAlmendra SCAmaranteAmaranthAmatic SCAmethystaAnaheimAndadaAndikaAngkorAnnie Use Your TelescopeAnonymous ProAnticAntic DidoneAntic SlabAntonArapeyArbutusArbutus SlabArchitects DaughterArchivo BlackArchivo NarrowArimoArizoniaArmataArtifikaArvoAsapAssetAstlochAsulAtomic AgeAubreyAudiowideAutour OneAverageAverage SansAveria Gruesa LibreAveria LibreAveria Sans LibreAveria Serif LibreBad ScriptBalthazarBangersBasicBattambangBaumansBayonBelgranoBellezaBenchNineBenthamBerkshire SwashBevanBigelow RulesBigshot OneBilboBilbo Swash CapsBitterBlack Ops OneBokorBonbonBoogalooBowlby OneBowlby One SCBrawlerBree SerifBubblegum SansBubbler OneBudaBuenardButchermanButterfly KidsCabinCabin CondensedCabin SketchCaesar DressingCagliostroCalligraffittiCamboCandalCantarellCantata OneCantora OneCapriolaCardoCarmeCarrois GothicCarrois Gothic SCCarter OneCaudexCedarville CursiveCeviche OneChanga OneChangoChau Philomene OneChela OneChelsea MarketChenlaCherry Cream SodaCherry SwashChewyChicleChivoCinzelCinzel DecorativeClicker ScriptCodaCoda CaptionCodystarComboComfortaaComing SoonConcert OneCondimentContentContrail OneConvergenceCookieCopseCorbenCourgetteCousineCoustardCovered By Your GraceCrafty GirlsCreepsterCrete RoundCrimson TextCroissant OneCrushedCuprumCutiveCutive MonoDaticoDancing ScriptDangrekDawning of a New DayDays OneDeliusDelius Swash CapsDelius UnicaseDella RespiraDenk OneDevonshireDidact GothicDiplomataDiplomata SCDomineDonegal OneDoppio OneDorsaDosisDr SugiyamaDroid SansDroid Sans MonoDroid SerifDuru SansDynalightEB GaramondEagle LakeEaterEconomicaElectrolizeElsieElsie Swash CapsEmblema OneEmilys CandyEngagementEnglebertEnriquetaErica OneEstebanEuphoria ScriptEwertExoExpletus SansFanwood TextFascinateFascinate InlineFaster OneFasthandFauna OneFederantFederoFelipaFenixFinger PaintFjalla OneFjord OneFlamencoFlavorsFondamentoFontdiner SwankyForumFrancois OneFreckle FaceFredericka the GreatFredoka OneFreehandFrescaFrijoleFrukturFugaz OneGFS DidotGFS NeohellenicGabrielaGafataGaldeanoGalindoGentium BasicGentium Book BasicGeoGeostarGeostar FillGermania OneGilda DisplayGive You GloryGlass AntiquaGlegooGloria HallelujahGoblin OneGochi HandGorditasGoudy Bookletter 1911GraduateGrand HotelGravitas OneGreat VibesGriffyGruppoGudeaHabibiHammersmith OneHanaleiHanalei FillHandleeHanumanHappy MonkeyHeadland OneHenny PennyHerr Von MuellerhoffHoltwood One SCHomemade AppleHomenajeIM Fell DW PicaIM Fell DW Pica SCIM Fell Double PicaIM Fell Double Pica SCIM Fell EnglishIM Fell English SCIM Fell French CanonIM Fell French Canon SCIM Fell Great PrimerIM Fell Great Primer SCIcebergIcelandImprimaInconsolataInderIndie FlowerInikaIrish GroverIstok WebItalianaItaliannoJacques FrancoisJacques Francois ShadowJim NightshadeJockey OneJolly LodgerJosefin SansJosefin SlabJoti OneJudsonJuleeJulius Sans OneJungeJuraJust Another HandJust Me Again Down HereKameronKarlaKaushan ScriptKavoonKeania OneKelly SlabKeniaKhmerKite OneKnewaveKotta OneKoulenKrankyKreonKristiKrona OneLailaLa Belle AuroreLancelotLatoLeague ScriptLeckerli OneLedgerLektonLemonLibre BaskervilleLife SaversLilita OneLily Script OneLimelightLinden HillLobsterLobster TwoLondrina OutlineLondrina ShadowLondrina SketchLondrina SolidLoraLove Ya Like A SisterLoved by the KingLovers QuarrelLuckiest GuyLusitanaLustriaMacondoMacondo Swash CapsMagraMaiden OrangeMakoMarcellusMarcellus SCMarck ScriptMargarineMarko OneMarmeladMarvelMateMate SCMaven ProMcLarenMeddonMedievalSharpMedula OneMegrimMeie ScriptMeriendaMerienda OneMerriweatherMerriweather SansMetalMetal ManiaMetamorphousMetrophobicMichromaMilongaMiltonianMiltonian TattooMiniverMiss FajardoseModern AntiquaMolengoMolleMondaMonofettMonotonMonsieur La DoulaiseMontagaMontezMontserratMontserrat AlternatesMontserrat SubrayadaMoulMoulpaliMountains of ChristmasMouse MemoirsMr BedfortMr DafoeMr De HavilandMrs Saint DelafieldMrs SheppardsMuliMystery QuestNeuchaNeutonNew RockerNews CycleNiconneNixie OneNobileNokoraNoricanNosiferNothing You Could DoNoticia TextNoto SansNoto SerifNova CutNova FlatNova MonoNova OvalNova RoundNova ScriptNova SlimNova SquareNumansNunitoOdor Mean CheyOffsideOld Standard TTOldenburgOleo ScriptOleo Script Swash CapsOpen SansOpen Sans CondensedOranienbaumOrbitronOreganoOrientaOriginal SurferOswaldOver the RainbowOverlockOverlock SCOvoOxygenOxygen MonoPT MonoPT SansPT Sans CaptionPT Sans NarrowPT SerifPT Serif CaptionPacificoPaprikaParisiennePassero OnePassion OnePathway Gothic OnePatrick HandPatrick Hand SCPatua OnePaytone OnePeraltaPermanent MarkerPetit Formal ScriptPetronaPhilosopherPiedraPinyon ScriptPirata OnePlasterPlayPlayballPlayfair DisplayPlayfair Display SCPodkovaPoiret OnePoller OnePolyPompierePontano SansPort Lligat SansPort Lligat SlabPrataPreahvihearPress Start 2PPrincess SofiaProcionoProsto OnePuritanPurple PurseQuandoQuanticoQuattrocentoQuattrocento SansQuestrialQuicksandQuintessentialQwigleyRacing Sans OneRadleyRalewayRaleway DotsRamblaRammetto OneRanchersRanchoRationaleRedressedReenie BeanieRevaliaRibeyeRibeye MarrowRighteousRisqueRobotoRoboto CondensedRoboto SlabRochesterRock SaltRokkittRomanescoRopa SansRosarioRosarivoRouge ScriptRudaRufinaRuge BoogieRulukoRum RaisinRuslan DisplayRusso OneRuthieRyeSacramentoSailSalsaSanchezSancreekSansita OneSarinaSatisfyScadaSchoolbellSeaweed ScriptSevillanaSeymour OneShadows Into LightShadows Into Light TwoShantiShareShare TechShare Tech MonoShojumaruShort StackSiemreapSigmar OneSignikaSignika NegativeSimonettaSintonySirin StencilSix CapsSkranjiSlackeySmokumSmytheSnigletSnippetSnowburst OneSofadi OneSofiaSonsie OneSorts Mill GoudySource Code ProSource Sans ProSpecial EliteSpicy RiceSpinnakerSpiraxSquada OneStalemateStalinist OneStardos StencilStint Ultra CondensedStint Ultra ExpandedStokeStraitSue Ellen FranciscoSunshineySupermercado OneSuwannaphumSwanky and Moo MooSyncopateTangerineTapromTauriTelexTenor SansText Me OneThe Girl Next DoorTienneTinosTitan OneTitillium WebTrade WindsTrocchiTrochutTrykkerTulpen OneUbuntuUbuntu CondensedUbuntu MonoUltraUncial AntiquaUnderdogUnica OneUnifrakturCookUnifrakturMaguntiaUnkemptUnlockUnnaVT323Vampiro OneVarelaVarela RoundVast ShadowViburVidalokaVigaVocesVolkhovVollkornVoltaireWaiting for the SunriseWallpoetWalter TurncoatWarnesWellfleetWendy OneWire OneYanone KaffeesatzYellowtailYeseva OneYesteryearZeyada
Font Weight Body
-- Default --
100
300
400
500
600
700
Background body show when use boxed layout
You can upload image for /themes/gavias_financial/images/patterns
Background Image
--Default--
az_subtle.pngblizzard.pngbright_squares.pngdenim.pngfancy_deboss.pnggray_jean.pnghoney_im_subtle.pnglinedpaper.pnglinen.pngpw_maze_white.pngrandom_grey_variations.pngskin_side_up.pngstitched_wool.pngstraws.pngsubtle_grunge.pngtextured_stripes.pngwild_oliva.pngworn_dots.png
Background Color
x
Background Position
--Default--
center top
center right
center bottom
center center
